https://www.spectrocell.com/privacy

Quartz Stopper Top FUV Cells
Black Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Black Semi-Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Micro FUV Cells
Semi-Micro FUV Cells
Super Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Micro Short Fluorometer NIR Cells
Black Micro Fluorometer NIR Cells (Self-masking)
Black Semi-Micro Fluorometer NIR Cells (Self-masking)
Glass / Quartz Grinding and Polishing
Glass Thermal Forming (Scientific Glass Blowing)
Home » Privacy Policy for Spectrocell Inc.
Privacy Policy for Spectrocell Inc.
Spectrocell Inc. respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "contact" form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of Spectrocell Inc.'s website and not sites that user’s access via links from our site. Spectrocell Inc. is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies
Spectrocell Inc.'s website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an e-mail with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Spectrocell Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Spectrocell Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Spectrocell Inc. and is effective as of October 1st, 2009. This statement does not create an agreement between Spectrocell Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
Contact Us
Spectrocell Inc.
143 Montgomery Ave.
Black Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Black Semi-Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Micro FUV Cells
Semi-Micro FUV Cells
Super Micro FUV Cells (Self-Masking)
Black Micro Fluorometer NIR Cells (Self-masking)
Black Semi-Micro Fluorometer NIR Cells (Self-masking)
Glass Thermal Forming (Scientific Glass Blowing)
Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions | Site Map | Site Credits: Ecreativeworks
